(Penny:)This is the best. You have booze with
breakfast on Tuesday, you got a problem.
(Penny:)You do it on the weekend,
you got brunch.
(Amy:)Sheldon doesn't believe in brunch.
Can't stand a table where one person's having
an omelet and another is having a sandwich.
That's not exhausting at all.
(Leonard:)Oh.
(Penny(receiving text):)It's Leonard. He says they're on the road
and headed for Bakersfield at warp speed.
(Penny(receiving text):)Maybe it's the mimosa,
but I'm gonna give the kid an LOL.
(Bernadette:)Cute how excited they are.
(Bernadette:)You should have seen Howard
sewing his costume all week.
(Amy:)When did Howard learn to sew?
When he was a little boy, every couple of
months he'd have to let his mom's pants out.
I don't understand
why they go to these conventions.
(Penny:)The four of them work at a major university,
they're all smart...
...how can they be into something
for 12-year-olds?
(Bernadette:)I don't mind it. I think Howie's
just in touch with his inner child.